neighborhoodlink.com 2008-05-14

# Neighborhood Link - Your Neighborhood's Privacy Practices

[](http://www.neighborhoodlink.com/) |  |  |  |  Neighborhood Link's   
Privacy Practices on the Web |   
---|---  
If you have questions regarding this privacy statement, please direct them to the Neighborhood Link staff ([privacy@neighborhoodlink.com](mailto:privacy@neighborhoodlink.com)). 

Neighborhood Link has created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to privacy. The following discloses our information gathering and dissemination practices for the Neighborhood Link Web site. 

**Personal Information**

It is Neighborhood Link's intention to give you as much control as possible over your personal information. In general, you can visit the Neighborhood Link Web site without telling us who you are or revealing any information about yourself. However, there are places on our Web site when we may need information from you, such as your name, email address, city/state, and zip code. It is our intent to let you know before we collect personal information from you. 

Neighborhood Link will not distribute or sell any of your personal information to third parties. However, your name, username, and email address are available to registered coordinators if you request coordinator access to the site. Only these three pieces of information are shared with them, nothing more. We do release account and other personal information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with law; enforce or apply our Terms of Use and other agreements; or protect the rights, property, or safety of Neighborhood Link, our users, or others.

1\. The IP address from which you post may be recorded by Neighborhood Link each time you post a comment or other information on a public area of the site, such as a message board. Neighborhood Link may therefore have the ability to link information about you together with information you may post for public review. 

2\. Neighborhood Link may be required to disclose information about you (see above) in response to subpoenas, warrants, court orders or legal process. 

3\. If Neighborhood Link receives a subpoena or other legal process requesting the disclosure of information about you, we will attempt to notify you before we respond, unless prohibited from doing so by a court order or applicable law. Specifically, 

a. We will attempt to notify you 30 days in advance of our response to such a subpoena or other legal process, or within a deadline set by a court order or applicable law, if that deadline is shorter than 30 days. 

b. We will attempt to notify you of such a subpoena or other legal process by sending a notice by electronic mail to the most recent e-mail address you have provided to us. The notice will include basic information concerning the subpoena, court order, or legal process (i.e., name of lawsuit, case number, place of filing, party issuing subpoena, the court where the subpoena was issued, contact information, deadline by which we plan to comply with the process, etc.). 

4\. If we receive a subpoena for your personal information (such as your identity), you may have the legal right to resist or limit the release of that information in court by filing a motion to quash the subpoena. You may be able to argue, for example, that disclosure of the information would violate your rights to free speech and privacy under the 1st and 4th Amendments of the U.S. Constitution. 

5\. We cannot advise you regarding the law or an appropriate response to a subpoena. Should you wish to oppose a subpoena or other legal process, you should seek legal advice concerning applicable rights and procedures that might be available. 

6\. If we receive a court-filed motion to quash or otherwise limit the subpoena from you or your lawyer, we will not disclose the requested information until we receive an order from the court to do so. 

We use your IP address to help diagnose problems with our server, and to administer our Web site. We also can use the IP address to verify the identity of perpetrators of illegal postings. 

We do keep track of the domains from which people visit us. Your domain address is used to gather broad demographic data. We analyze this data for trends and statistics, and then we discard it. 

The Neighborhood Link Web site's registration forms (only found in certain areas of our site) require users to give us contact information (like their name and email address). We use the contact information from registration forms to send information about Neighborhood Link and to insure that our programming is used for legitimate purposes (see our Terms of Use). The contact information is also used to contact the visitor when necessary. Visitors may opt-out of receiving future communications (see below). 

**Public Forums**  
The Neighborhood Link Web site makes chat rooms, forums, and message boards available to its visitors. Please remember that any information that is disclosed in these areas becomes public information, please exercise caution when deciding to disclose your personal information. Neighborhood Link may post the transcript of a chat session on a Web site or other media for informational, example, or demonstration purposes. 

**Security**  
The Neighborhood Link Web site has security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse and alteration of the information under our control. We back up the entire Neighborhood Link Web site on a daily basis, and have password protected access levels which insure legitimate site administration. 

**Business relationships**  
The Neighborhood Link Web site contains links to other Web sites. Neighborhood Link is not responsible for the security practices of the Web sites that are linked from our site. We highly recommend that visitors check the privacy statements at these linked sites. 

**Cookies**  
There is a technology called "cookies" which can be used to provide you with tailored information from a Web site. A cookie is an element of data that a Web site can send to your browser, which may then store it on your system. Some Neighborhood Link pages use cookies so that we can better serve you when you visit and then return to our site. We use cookies to deliver information specific to your interests and to save your password so you don't have to re-enter it each time you visit certain areas of our Web site. 

**Choice/Opt-out**  
The Neighborhood Link Web site provides visitors, with the exception of Neighborhood Coordinators, the opportunity to opt-out of receiving communications from us. Neighborhood Coordinators agree to receive communication from Neighborhood Link for as long as they are coordinators. Visitors who would like not to receive any communication from Neighborhood Link, please email [info@neighborhoodlink.com](mailto:info@neighborhoodlink.com), or visit your [profile page](http://www.neighborhoodlink.com/manager/usersystem/userManage.html). 

**Modify Your Information**  
The Neighborhood Link Web site provides visitors with the opportunity to change or modify information previously provided. If you would like to change or modify your information, please email [info@neighborhoodlink.com](mailto:info@neighborhoodlink.com), or visit your [profile page](http://www.neighborhoodlink.com/manager/usersystem/userManage.html). 

If we make any material changes to our privacy practices or if we are going to use your personally identifiable information in a manner different from that stated in our privacy policy at the time of collection, we will notify you via email regardless of your privacy settings. We will also post a revised privacy page 30 days prior to any change.

If you have any questions or comments about this privacy statement, the practices of this Web site, or your dealings with Neighborhood Link, you can contact the Neighborhood Link staff at [privacy@neighborhoodlink.com](mailto:privacy@neighborhoodlink.com). 

Neighborhood Link [Terms of Use](http://www.neighborhoodlink.com/manager/neighbor/terms.html)   
© 1997 - 2006 Neighborhood Link, Inc.
